<root>
  <dayWiseIternaries>
    <iternaries>
      <id>9188454c-ac4a-4010-a018-721b75033e44</id>
      <dayNumber>1</dayNumber>
      <dayDate/>
      <packageName>australia’s-northern-territory</packageName>
      <dayImage/>
      <slotDetails> Darwin: Arrive at the airport. Transfer to your hotel and check-in. Rest of the day at leisure. Overnight in Darwin.</slotDetails>
    </iternaries>
  </dayWiseIternaries>
  <dayWiseIternaries>
    <iternaries>
      <id>fb94e646-5fe8-4a95-aa70-57552741202f</id>
      <dayNumber>2</dayNumber>
      <dayDate/>
      <packageName>australia’s-northern-territory</packageName>
      <dayImage/>
      <slotDetails> Darwin: After breakfast, the coach will pick you up from your hotel for the departure point of your full day tour to Kakadu National Park. Depart Darwin and travel across Adelaide River and Marrakai Plains into World Heritage-listed Kakadu National Park, a timeless place &amp; landscape filled with beauty and diversity. Visit the Warradjan Cultural Center &amp; view the informative displays depicting the traditions of the Aboriginal people in Kakadu. Then join a local guide for a cruise on the famous Yellow Water Billabong. Search for saltwater crocodiles &amp; the colorful range of birdlife for which this region is renowned. After a lunch stop at Nourlangie Rock, your guide will lead a walk to view ancient Aboriginal rock art before commencing the return journey to Darwin for overnight. (B)</slotDetails>
    </iternaries>
  </dayWiseIternaries>
  <dayWiseIternaries>
    <iternaries>
      <id>d0f52810-dd99-4f12-9b7e-ae79b16f5f3c</id>
      <dayNumber>3</dayNumber>
      <dayDate/>
      <packageName>australia’s-northern-territory</packageName>
      <dayImage/>
      <slotDetails>Darwin: After breakfast, the coach will pick you up from your hotel for your full day tour to Litchfield National Park. Litchfield National Park contains several types of typical Top End habitats including lush monsoon forests, termite mounds, unusual rock formations, waterfalls, and cascades. Follow the Stuart Highway via the township of Batchelor to Litchfield National Park to visit the main falls. First stop is Florence Falls, where you will have the opportunity for a scenic and interpretive bush and monsoon vine forest walk. There is also the chance for a swim. Then travel to Tolmer Falls for views of the water cascading down to the deep waterhole at the base of the falls. Stop for lunch before continuing to the rock pool at Wangi Falls, where time is available for a swim. Re-board the coach and return to Darwin for overnight. (B)</slotDetails>
    </iternaries>
  </dayWiseIternaries>
  <dayWiseIternaries>
    <iternaries>
      <id>276ab2cb-fe3d-4c0b-bccc-0736570231a4</id>
      <dayNumber>4</dayNumber>
      <dayDate/>
      <packageName>australia’s-northern-territory</packageName>
      <dayImage/>
      <slotDetails>Darwin – Ayers Rock: After breakfast, check-out &amp; transfer from hotel to airport for your flight (not included) to Ayers Rock. Arrive at the airport. Transfer to your hotel &amp; check-in. Rest of the day at leisure till Uluru Base &amp; Sunset tour. The coach will pick you up from your hotel to commence an afternoon Uluru Base and Sunset tour. Travel around the base of Uluru &amp; listen to commentary about the numerous sacred sites &amp; features to be found at Uluru. Continue to the Kuniya Walk where your driver guide will escort you to the beautiful Mutitjulu Waterhole. View Aboriginal rock paintings &amp; learn about the native flora, &amp; the Aboriginal &amp; European history of Uluru. Later visit the Uluru-Kata Tjuta Cultural Center where you can learn more about Aboriginal culture &amp; see Aboriginal arts &amp; crafts. In the late afternoon travel to the Uluru sunset viewing area to witness the striking colour changes of Uluru at sunset whilst enjoying nibbles &amp; a glass of wine. Tour concludes approximately 30 minutes after sunset. Back to the hotel for overnight in Ayers Rock. (B)</slotDetails>
    </iternaries>
  </dayWiseIternaries>
  <dayWiseIternaries>
    <iternaries>
      <id>156e288c-9aa7-4b31-80b5-ada3b2b5ee8f</id>
      <dayNumber>5</dayNumber>
      <dayDate/>
      <packageName>australia’s-northern-territory</packageName>
      <dayImage/>
      <slotDetails>Ayers Rock: Early morning, the coach will pick you up from your hotel to commence a morning Uluru Sunrise and Kata Tjuta tour (Departure Time: 90 minutes prior to sunrise). Travel to the sunrise viewing area, Talinguru Nyakunytjaku, and watch the first rays of sunlight creep across the desert plains. Enjoy a cup of tea or coffee &amp; biscuits as the morning sun slowly changes the colour of Uluru. After watching the sunrise travel to the mystical 36 domes of Kata Tjuta enjoying panoramic views of the southern side of Kata Tjuta before arriving at the base of Walpa Gorge. Spend time exploring the gorge &amp; the unusual conglomerate rock formations. The walking trail through Walpa Gorge follows the natural creek between two of the tallest domes of Kata Tjuta. The rest of the day at leisure for optional activities. Overnight in Ayers Rock.</slotDetails>
    </iternaries>
  </dayWiseIternaries>
  <dayWiseIternaries>
    <iternaries>
      <id>bc3a6816-e96f-4226-bffe-4eaea2f3b5ee</id>
      <dayNumber>6</dayNumber>
      <dayDate/>
      <packageName>australia’s-northern-territory</packageName>
      <dayImage/>
      <slotDetails>Ayers Rock- Alice Springs: Today, check-out &amp; transfer from hotel to the airport for your flight (not included) to Alice Springs. Arrive at the airport. Transfer to your hotel &amp; check-in. Rest of the day at leisure. Overnight in Alice Springs.</slotDetails>
    </iternaries>
  </dayWiseIternaries>
  <dayWiseIternaries>
    <iternaries>
      <id>c808ec6d-43c7-48a6-bbf8-7994b1168b68</id>
      <dayNumber>7</dayNumber>
      <dayDate/>
      <packageName>australia’s-northern-territory</packageName>
      <dayImage/>
      <slotDetails>Alice Springs: Today, the coach will pick you up from your hotel to commence a full day West MacDonnell Ranges tour. Experience the magnificent grandeur of the West MacDonnell Ranges, the deep red cleft of Standley Chasm, the mystique of Ellery Creek Big Hole &amp; the cultural significance of the Ochre Pits. Enjoy a Ploughman’s lunch at Glen Helen Resort. After lunch visit Glen Helen Gorge, Ormiston Gorge &amp; see the immense cliffs of quartzite at Simpsons Gap where you have the opportunity to see the black-footed rock wallabies. Back to the hotel overnight in Alice Springs.</slotDetails>
    </iternaries>
  </dayWiseIternaries>
  <dayWiseIternaries>
    <iternaries>
      <id>334869d3-aa32-4739-bc38-887fc6d1c447</id>
      <dayNumber>8</dayNumber>
      <dayDate/>
      <packageName>australia’s-northern-territory</packageName>
      <dayImage/>
      <slotDetails>Alice Springs: Today, check-out and transfer from hotel to the airport for your next destination.</slotDetails>
    </iternaries>
  </dayWiseIternaries>
</root>