<root>
  <dayWiseIternaries>
    <iternaries>
      <id>01c4bc88-0149-4dbf-a7b1-06fdc35accf4</id>
      <dayNumber>1</dayNumber>
      <dayDate/>
      <packageName>glimpses-of-muscat</packageName>
      <dayImage/>
      <slotDetails> Muscat : Arrive Muscat International Airport. Our English-speaking representative would meet you at the arrival hall with a paging board. Transfer to your hotel in Muscat. This short drive to your hotel would provide you the first impressions of a clean and green capital. During the drive our driver/guide would enlighten you with some basic facts about the Muscat and Oman in general. Check-in at the hotel. Overnight in Oman.</slotDetails>
    </iternaries>
  </dayWiseIternaries>
  <dayWiseIternaries>
    <iternaries>
      <id>4c586a4e-2450-4791-99d8-e0ce8bc8ae95</id>
      <dayNumber>2</dayNumber>
      <dayDate/>
      <packageName>glimpses-of-muscat</packageName>
      <dayImage/>
      <slotDetails>Muscat : After breakfast, Today you can explore Muscat, the clean capital city. A unique blend of the ancient &amp; the modern, Muscat is a beautiful clean city, which lies in the middle of a maze of brown pleated mountains, lulled by the Arabian Sea. The city has undergone dramatic development in the past two or three decades, however it has never lost its pride in its heritage &amp; culture. You can start our tour with a visit to the Grand Mosque, which is an architectural marvel and is perhaps the new landmark of the city. You can continue your drive through the ministries area where you can see a number of modern buildings with touches of Islamic architecture. A drive a drive along the corniche will take you to Old Muscat. Take a special tour of one of the most popular places of Muscat – enchanting Muttrah souq with its narrow covered alleys where the exotic smells of mounds of spices, coffees, ancient remedies and enticing perfumes fill the air. Explore the winding and zigzag alleys for a good bargain! You can visit the Bait Al Zubair Museum or Bait Al Baranda Museum, which has a fine exhibit of Omani history and culture. You would have a photo stop at the magnificent Al Aalam Palace (the official residence of Sultan Qaboos) flanked by the twin Portuguese forts of Mirani &amp; Jalali. Return to hotel. Afternoon at leisure. Overnight in Oman. (B)</slotDetails>
    </iternaries>
  </dayWiseIternaries>
  <dayWiseIternaries>
    <iternaries>
      <id>3ae3da11-c294-4167-b12e-2a0a63563ef2</id>
      <dayNumber>3</dayNumber>
      <dayDate/>
      <packageName>glimpses-of-muscat</packageName>
      <dayImage/>
      <slotDetails>Muscat : After breakfast, proceed to Dunes of Wahiba. Running south from the Eastern Hajjar Mountains to Arabian Sea, the Wahiba Sands, described a Sand sea, stretches almost 200 kms in length &amp; about 100 kms in width. The dunes rise above 100-150 meters in different shades of color and shifting sands, is the perfect place for both the romantic and the adventurous. There are still Bedouin families living in this vast expanse of sands. A roller-coaster ride over the dunes would be thrilling and fun especially for those who are first time visitors to the desert. The trip also includes a refreshing visit to the lush pools of Wadi Bani Khalid. Overnight stay at the hotel. (B)</slotDetails>
    </iternaries>
  </dayWiseIternaries>
  <dayWiseIternaries>
    <iternaries>
      <id>f9c397f5-43c8-475a-9a8e-50d7dc7f40e3</id>
      <dayNumber>4</dayNumber>
      <dayDate/>
      <packageName>glimpses-of-muscat</packageName>
      <dayImage/>
      <slotDetails> Muscat : After breakfast day is at leisure at the hotel until our representative meets you to be transferred to the Muscat Airport for your departure flight. (B)</slotDetails>
    </iternaries>
  </dayWiseIternaries>
</root>