
<root>
  <dayWiseIternaries>
    <iternaries>
      <id>528a52b0-b24e-4272-b821-cb1b24bff5f1</id>
      <dayNumber>1</dayNumber>
      <dayDate/>
      <packageName>singapore-sentosa-getaway</packageName>
      <dayImage/>
      <dayDetails>Sentosa: Arrive in Singapore. Meet &amp; greet, transfer to Sentosa hotel. Free at leisure the rest of the day. Overnight in Singapore Sentosa.</dayDetails>
    </iternaries>
  </dayWiseIternaries>
  <dayWiseIternaries>
    <iternaries>
      <id>438694a0-a9bb-4047-8c6d-7ac70c214a52</id>
      <dayNumber>2</dayNumber>
      <dayDate/>
      <packageName>singapore-sentosa-getaway</packageName>
      <dayImage/>
      <dayDetails>Sentosa: Breakfast at the hotel. Whether you’re a thrillseeker, nature lover, or simply out for some family fun, there’s definitely something for you with the Day FUN Pass Play Max, which offers you the freedom to cover up to 20 exciting attractions : 4D Adventureland : Desperados in 4D, Extreme Log Ride and Journey 2: The Mysterious Island. Bi-Pedal Bicycle (2 Hours). Butterfly Park and Insect Kingdom. MegaBounce or Parajump @ Mega Adventure. MOSH!. Segway® Fun Ride (2 Rides). Sentosa Merlion Skyline Luge Sentosa (1 Luge and 1 Skyride). Singapore Cable Car – Sentosa Line ONLY. Tiger Sky Tower. Trick Eye Museum Singapore. Wave House Sentosa – Catch-A-Wave (1 Try). Wings of Time (Standard Seat). Images of Singapore LIVE and Madame Tussauds Singapore (2-in-1 Combo). S.E.A. Aquarium™. K-Live Sentosa (Hologram). Return back to the hotel with lots of memories. Overnight in Singapore Sentosa. (B)</dayDetails>
    </iternaries>
  </dayWiseIternaries>
  <dayWiseIternaries>
    <iternaries>
      <id>8565009d-c031-4be9-873d-5cb76a7763a0</id>
      <dayNumber>3</dayNumber>
      <dayDate/>
      <packageName>singapore-sentosa-getaway</packageName>
      <dayImage/>
      <dayDetails>Sentosa: After breakfast, the day is free for shopping or you can explore the Island. Overnight in Singapore Sentosa. (B)</dayDetails>
    </iternaries>
  </dayWiseIternaries>
  <dayWiseIternaries>
    <iternaries>
      <id>f3714f27-15e2-40d7-a1c2-5a7385367201</id>
      <dayNumber>4</dayNumber>
      <dayDate/>
      <packageName>singapore-sentosa-getaway</packageName>
      <dayImage/>
      <dayDetails>Sentosa: Breakfast at the hotel. Check-out and transfer to the airport for your onwards journey. (B).</dayDetails>
    </iternaries>
  </dayWiseIternaries>
</root>