<root>
  <dayWiseIternaries>
    <iternaries>
      <id>3923a29f-1732-45a8-bd76-1d09b0230381</id>
      <dayNumber>1</dayNumber>
      <dayDate/>
      <packageName>Spectacular Thailand</packageName>
      <dayImage>1565349531750_25463_og_1.jpeg</dayImage>
      <slotDetails>Arrive Phuket :
On arrival at the Phuket International airport you will be met and transferred to the hotel in Phuket. Check into the hotel. It is the jewel of the Andaman Sea and a popular tropical beach resort. The rest of the day is at leisure. Overnight at the hotel in Phuket. (B)
</slotDetails>
    </iternaries>
  </dayWiseIternaries>
  <dayWiseIternaries>
    <iternaries>
      <id>26c81c38-7017-44ed-9306-70018d3a00e8</id>
      <dayNumber>2</dayNumber>
      <dayDate/>
      <packageName>Spectacular Thailand</packageName>
      <dayImage>1565349543506_Krabi-Phi-Phi-is-part-of-Mu-Ko-Phi-Phi-National-Park-1000x667.jpg</dayImage>
      <slotDetails>Phuket - Phi Phi Island Tour
Today proceed for Phi Phi Island tour by Phi Phi - 4 Hours tour by longtails Enjoy a day on the classic white beaches, surrounded by impressive limestone cliffs and sunlit crystal water. Later in the afternoon return back to Phuket. Overnight at the hotel in PhiPhi Island . (B)
</slotDetails>
    </iternaries>
  </dayWiseIternaries>
  <dayWiseIternaries>
    <iternaries>
      <id>617fa070-a3e0-4133-8a5f-57d3aa1489c9</id>
      <dayNumber>3</dayNumber>
      <dayDate/>
      <packageName>Spectacular Thailand</packageName>
      <dayImage>1565349549749_Banana-Beach.jpg</dayImage>
      <slotDetails>Phuket – Banana Beach
Today proceed to  Phuket  Banana Beach @ Koh Hey by speed boat with Snorkling and Clear Kayaks, the most relaxing and enjoyable day outs for tourist staying in Phuket. Overnight at Hotel in Phuket (B )
</slotDetails>
    </iternaries>
  </dayWiseIternaries>
  <dayWiseIternaries>
    <iternaries>
      <id>b212d023-3dc0-4775-b161-cca697bf5302</id>
      <dayNumber>4</dayNumber>
      <dayDate/>
      <packageName>Spectacular Thailand</packageName>
      <dayImage>1565349559441_4 island tour 2019.png</dayImage>
      <slotDetails>Phuket – Krabi Four Island Tour : 
Today after breakfast proceed to Krabi .On arrival at the Krabi International airport you will be met and transferred to the hotel in Krabi. Check into the hotel.  Enjoy an island hopping tour of the four islands by speed boat. It is an exciting island-hopping to the tropical hot spots in the Krabi Sea. Visit the Tub Island, Chicken Island, Poda Island and the Pranang Cave. Swimming, Snorkel, Sunbathing, exploring and photography are the main activities to enjoy. Expect plenty of sun, a rich variety of coral and fishes, crystal clear waters and white powdery sand beaches, lined with exotic coconut palms. Return back to the hotel. Overnight at the hotel in Krabi. (B, L)
</slotDetails>
    </iternaries>
  </dayWiseIternaries>
  <dayWiseIternaries>
    <iternaries>
      <id>bd4c6390-11aa-485e-8a80-23d0524502aa</id>
      <dayNumber>5</dayNumber>
      <dayDate/>
      <packageName>Spectacular Thailand</packageName>
      <dayImage>1565349579949_036ac5144cc0e3b2d8421c6099fbd375.jpg</dayImage>
      <slotDetails> Krabi :
Today the day will be at leisure. Overnight at the Hotel in Krabi (B).

</slotDetails>
    </iternaries>
  </dayWiseIternaries>
  <dayWiseIternaries>
    <iternaries>
      <id>34b621d1-e631-4ad0-943b-b367b0883170</id>
      <dayNumber>6</dayNumber>
      <dayDate/>
      <packageName>Spectacular Thailand</packageName>
      <dayImage/>
      <slotDetails>Depart Krabi :
Today after breakfast, check out well in time proceed to Krabi / Phuket Airport and board the return flight to home. (B)
</slotDetails>
    </iternaries>
  </dayWiseIternaries>
</root>